Jorge Enrique Sala Ac

Full Stack Developer

jorge.e.sala@gmail.com | +52 9831381485 | Mérida, México | Linkedin | Github Open to relocation

PROFILE

Full Stack developer with 2+ years of experience with web applications, creation of websites using HTML, CSS and React, creation of APIs using Spring Boot with JPA and Spring Security. Successfully delivered projects independently and as part of a collaborative team. Seeking a professional opportunity to apply my technical skills in a dynamic, challenging, and constantly growing environment.

SKILLS

Technical Skills: Java | Spring Boot | JPA | Hibernate | Spring Security | Kafka | React | Javascript | Html | CSS | Typescript | Tailwind CSS | RESTful APIs | SQL | AWS | Docker | Scrum | Git | Github | Jira | Postman

Soft Skills: Teamwork | Communication | Problem solving | Leadership | Attention to detail | Proactivity | Time management

WORK EXPERIENCE

Papelería y novedades "Teresita" (Certification project)

Full Stack Developer / Product Owner

February 2024 - May 2024

- I developed a RESTful API using Java, Spring Boot, JPA, and Spring Security to manage database access for various user types.
- I served as the Product Owner for an e-commerce project for my own store. We utilized platforms like Trello and Figma to stay organized and follow the Scrum methodology.
- I integrated the backend and frontend of the application by utilizing JavaScript to consume REST APIs, efficiently managing and processing data to ensure seamless communication between both layers.

Iktansoft

Web developer

June 2018 - December 2018

- I made a web application using HTML, CSS, Javascript and jQuery to measure the distance between 2 points in a 3d model given a 3d file and the size it would have in real life.
- I enhanced the user interface of a web application by implementing a mockup created by a designer. For this I used HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and jQuery and AJAX.
- I developed multiple scripts using C# within a 3D modeling software. These scripts utilized the data from the 3D models to generate JSON files, which were then used to create report files for the models.

EDUCATION

Generation Mexico

Full Stack Java developer

February 2024 - May 2024

Accenture Cobol developer

March 2023 - April 2023

Accenture Java developer

February 2023 - March 2023

Universidad Autónoma de Yucatán (UADY) Software Engineering

2015 - 2024

LANGUAGES

• Spanish (Native) English (Advanced)